Guide to the Undergraduate Affairs, Yale College, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Dean of Undergraduate Affairs, 1956-1987; Accession 1989-A-029
  - Office Files and Reports
    - Black Women in Post-Secondary Education, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 417)
    - Broadcast Music, Inc. (BMI), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 419)
    - Center for Independent Study, Inc., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 420)
    - Chicano Students, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 421)
    - Class of '83--Profile, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 422)
    - Class of '82--Profile, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 423)
    - Profile of the Class of 1981, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 424)
    - Closing of College--Check-out Procedures, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 425)
    - Committees, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 426)
    - Concerns, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 427)
    - Concerns Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 428)
    - Corning (Houghton) Travelling Fellowship, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 429 - 430)
    - Dean's Advisory Committee on Undergraduate Organizations, 1971-1982 (Box 4, Folder 431)
    - Dwight Hall, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 432)
    - Fellows, Trumbull, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 433)
    - Financial Aid, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 434)
    - Freshman Advisees, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 435)
    - Freshman Mailing, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 436)
    - Freshman Planner The Blue Alert, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 437)
    - Honors and Special Projects Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 438)
    - Incidents
      - 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 439)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 440)
    - Junior Year Abroad Program, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 441)
    - Legal Issues, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 442)
    - Confidential--Grievance Report, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 443)
    - Marnesba M. Hill Fellowship Fund, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 444)
    - Council of Masters, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 445)
    - Minority Advisory Council, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 446 - 447)
    - Deans Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 448)
    - Residential College Deans Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 449)
    - Senior Class Dues, Activities, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 450)
    - Social Fee Arrangements, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 451)
    - Sponsors for Educational Opportunity, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 452)
    - Student Census Report Submitted by the Residential Colleges of Yale University, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 453)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 454)
    - Yale College Standing Committees, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 455)
    - Recommendations
      - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 456)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 457)
    - Report of the Minority Student Development Project, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 458)
    - Residential College Deans Meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 459)
    - Dahl Report, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 460)
    - Dining Halls (Policy), 1978 (Box 5, Folder 462)
    - Disciplinary Memoranda, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 463)
    - Correspondence Within Yale
      - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 464)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 465)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 466)
    - Correspondence With Other Universities
      - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 467)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 468)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 469)
    - Correspondence--Miscellaneous
      - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 470)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 471)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 472)
    - Council of Masters
      - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 473)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 474)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 475)
    - Report of the Committee on Economic Status of the Yale Faculty, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 476)
    - Report of the Study Committee on Yale College, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 477)
    - Minority Advisory Council, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 478)
    - Minority Faculty, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 479)
    - Minority Students--General, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 480)
    - Minority Students, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 481)
    - Minority Student Retention Program, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 482)
    - Minority Undergraduates, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 483)
    - Minority Student Graduate School Name Exchange, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 484)
    - New England Minority Women Administrators
      - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 485)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 486)
    - Personnel, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 487)
    - Police Advisory Board
      - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 488 - 489)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 490)
    - Police Reports
      - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 491)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 492)
    - Postgraduate Planning, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 493)
    - Proposals for the Improvement of Teaching in Yale College, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 494)
    - Readmission, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 495)
    - Undergraduate Organizations Financial Orientation Meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 496)
    - PRC Exchange Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 497)
    - Use of University Facility Requests--Miscellaneous, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 498)
    - Yale Station Display Cases--Letters of Application Granted, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 499)
    - Fundraising Policy, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 500)
    - Old Campus Events, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 501)
    - Dramats, Residential College, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 502)
    - Yale Station Display Cases
      - Letters of Application Pending, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 503)
      - Contracts, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 504)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Organizations, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 505)
    - Poster Violations--Miscellaneous File, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 506)
    - Undergraduate Organizations--Proposed, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 507)
    - Undergraduate Organizations Policy, 1978-1983 (Box 5, Folder 508)
    - Funding Requests Approved, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 509)
    - Office of the Secretary, Groups Registered with, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 510)
    - Poster Policy, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 511)
    - Woolsey Hall, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 512)
    - Woolsey Hall--Applications for Use, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 513)
    - Space for Undergraduate Organizations, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 514)
    - Poster Violations--Fines, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 515)
    - Undergraduate Organizations Funding--End-of-Year Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 516)
    - Yale Station Display Case Contracts, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 517)
    - Use of Yale Name--Policy, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 518)
    - Housing, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 519)
    - Yale Musical Theatre: Finances, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 520)
    - Yale Dramat--Finances, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 521)
    - Space, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 522)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Organizations, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 523)
- Records of the Associate Dean for Student Affairs, Yale College, 1971-1988; Accession 1990-A-016
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2024
  - A.I.E.S.E.C., 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Alley Cats, Yale, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alliance, The, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alph Phi Alpha Fraternity, Zeta Chapter, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5 - 6)
  - Alph Sigma Phi Fraternity, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Amateur Radio Club Newsletter: Vol. 1 No. 6, Vol. 1 No. 1, Vol. 11 No. 2, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Amateur Radio Society, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Field Service (AFS), 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Asian American Students Alliance (AASA), 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Asian American Students Association, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Atlas, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Aurelian Honor Society, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Aurora Magazine, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15 - 16)
  - Bach Society, The Yale, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Baker's Dozen, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Baptist Student Union, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Berkeley Dramat, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Berkeley People's Film Society, 1979-1986 (Box 1, Folder 21 - 22)
  - Beyond War Project, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 23 - 24)
  - Black Alliance at Yale (BSAY), 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Black Ivy, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Black and White: A Yale Undergraduate Photography Journal, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 27 - 28)
  - Blue Moon, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Business Bulletin Yale, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 30 - 31)
  - Business and Economic Forum, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 32 - 33)
  - Canadian Students Association, Yale, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Caribbean Club at Yale, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Charities Drive, Yale, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 36 - 37)
  - Chess Club at Yale, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 38 - 40)
  - China - (Yale) Association Student Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Christian Fellowship, Yale, 1971-1986 (Box 1, Folder 42 - 43)
  - Clan na Gael, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 44 - 45)
  - Coalition Against Apartheid, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Coalition for an Educated Choice, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - College Colloquium, Yale, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - College Council, Yale, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 49 - 55)
  - College Handbook, Yale, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - College Democrats, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 57 - 58)
  - College Republicans, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 59 - 60)
  - Community of Women Athletics, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Creative Loafing, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Currents, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Daily News, Yale, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 64 - 67)
  - Dancers, Yale, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 68 - 69)
  - Debate Association, 1982-1986 (Box 1, Folder 70 - 72)
  - Despierta Boricua, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Draft and Registration Information Service, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Dramat Children's Theater, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 75 - 76)
  - Dramatic Association, University, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 77 - 81)
  - Duke's Men of Yale, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Dwight Hall Student Cabinet, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Economic and Business Review, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 84 - 85)
  - Equal Access for Students at Yale, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Exit Players, The, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Film Quarterly, The Yale, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Film Society, Yale, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Free Press, Yale, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Freshman Outdoor Orientation Trips, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 91 - 92)
  - Gays, Bisexual and Lesbians of Color, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Gay and Lesbian Co-operative, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Gay Students' Center at Yale, 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 95 - 97)
  - Gilbert and Sullivan Society, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 98 - 99)
  - Gospel Choir, Yale, 1979-1986 (Box 2, Folder 100 - 101)
  - Herald, The Yale, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 102 - 103)
  - Heritage Theatre Ensemble, 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 104 - 105)
  - Hunger Action Project, Yale, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 106 - 107)
  - Independent Party, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Interactions: Society Organized Against Racism, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - International Forum at Yale, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 110 - 111)
  - International Relations, Incorporated, 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 112 - 114)
  - Joint Council of Social Chairs, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 115 - 116)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Kayaking Club (lacking), 1982 (Box 2)
  - Korean-American Journal, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Kosher Kitchen, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - La Herencia Latina, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Law School Film Society, Yale, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Liberal Party of the Yale Political Union, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 124 - 125)
  - Living Water, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Maya's Room: Silliman College Art Gallery, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 127 - 129)
  - Men's Caucus, The, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Mime Troupe, The Yale, 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 131 - 132)
  - Mixed Company, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Mountaineering Club, Yale, 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 134 - 135)
  - Movimiento Estudiantil Chicano de Aztlan (MEChA), 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 136 - 137)
  - Musical Theatre, Yale, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 138 - 139)
  - Nadine Magazine, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 140 - 141)
  - New Blue, The, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - New Journal, The, 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 143 - 145)
  - Nichiren Shoshu Student Group, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 146 - 147)
  - Objectivism Study Group, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Occasional Stiles and Yale Art Review, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Orthodox Christian Fellowship at Yale, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 150 - 151)
  - Outdoor Corps: Finances, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Outing Club, The, 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 153 - 154)
  - Park Street 211, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Party of the Right, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - People of El Salvador, The Committee in Solidarity with the, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Political Monthly, Yale, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 158 - 159)
  - Political Union, The Yale, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 160 - 163)
  - Polytechnic Preparatory School Club, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Prism, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Progressive Zionist Caucus, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Proof of the Pudding, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Purple Crayon of Yale, The, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Queue Magazine, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Record, The Yale, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 170 - 172)
  - Recycling, Yale, 1979-1986 (Box 2, Folder 173 - 174)
  - Redhot and Blue, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Response, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Rhetorician, The Yale: a Student Forum, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 177 - 178)
  - Ritual and Dissent, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Rumor, The, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Russian Chorus, Yale, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 181 - 182)
  - Sanctuary Project, The, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - Scientific Publications, Yale, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 184 - 186)
  - Sigma Chi Fraternity / The Old Campus, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - Slavic Chorus, Yale, 1980-1986 (Box 3, Folder 188 - 189)
  - Soar, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Society of Orpheus and Bacchus, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Something Extra, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - South Asian Society, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Speaker's Corner, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Spectrum Film Society, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Spizzwinks, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Students
    - Animal Rights Coalition, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - Art Society, Yale (formerly Art Organization), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - Bridge Club, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - Campaign Against Hunger, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - Chapter of Amnesty International, 1979-1984 (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - Chapter of Campus Crusade for Christ, 1980-1986 (Box 3, Folder 202 - 203)
    - Communiversity Day, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - Danceworks at Yale, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - Directory, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - Effort to Alleviate Suffering, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 207 - 208)
    - Friends of Israel, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 209 - 210)
    - Friends of Peace Now / Progressive Zionist Students at Yale, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Guide to Yale and New Haven, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Gynecological Resource, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - Investment Group, Yale College, 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 214 - 216)
    - Life, for (formerly Pro-Life Coalition), 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 217 - 218)
    - Military Association, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - Nuclear Disarmament, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 220 - 221)
    - Panamerican Society, Yale, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 222)
    - Pugwash at Yale, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 223)
    - Speech Association (formerly Yale Society for Creative Discourse), 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 224 - 225)
  - Sub Rosa, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - Tory Party, The, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Trips for Outdoor Enjoyment, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Undergraduate
    - Art Gallery, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 229)
    - Course Critique, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 230 - 231)
    - Economic Groups, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 232)
    - Forum, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 233 - 235)
    - Global Forum, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 236)
    - Organizations, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 237 - 238)
    - Pan-hellenic Association, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 239)
    - Women's Caucus, 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 240 - 242)
    - Zircus Literary Journal, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - University Pictures, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - Walden: Student to Student Counseling, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 245 - 246)
  - Whiffenpoofs, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - Whim 'n Rhythm, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - Women's Athletic Organization, YWAO Sports Magazine, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 249 - 250)
  - Women's Center Resource, The Yale, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - Women's Theater Project (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - Yale, The, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - Yale Banner, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 254 - 255)
  - Yale-China Association, a Student Committee, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Yale-USSR Project, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - Yale Standard, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - Yalesbians, 1980-1986 (Box 3, Folder 259 - 260)
  - Young Israel House at Yale, 1980-1986 (Box 3, Folder 261 - 263)
- Records of the Associate Dean for Student Affairs, 1969-1990; Accession 1990-A-157
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025
  - Academic Calendar, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Development, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Accounting and Finances, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Advisees, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center (AACC)
    - General, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Director's Search, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Alcohol Forum (Yale College Council), 1985 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Alcohol Policy Publicity, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Service Policy, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Annapolis Conference, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Associated Student Agencies (ASA):
    - General, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Council, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Association of Yale Alumni (AYA):
    - General, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Assembly: "Student Organizations", 1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Assembly: "Yale Athletics", 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Band, Yale, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Beckham Guide for Black Students, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Bingham - Hendrie Hall / Space Allocation Issues, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Buckley Amendment: Policy Statement, Student Records, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - University Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Bursar's Office, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Casa Cultural Julia de Burgos
    - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Census (Student), 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Chaplain's Office, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Class Profile
    - 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 1986 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Committee on Academic Development, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Committee on Freedom of Expression at Yale, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Committee on Honors and Academic Standing
    - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Committees on Yale College, Standing
    - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Committee on Yale College Student Life, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Communiversity Day, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Computer Infractions, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, Inter-Office Memos, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence with Other Colleges, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Council of Masters, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 295-297 Crown St., 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Dean's Association, New England, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Dean's Group Meeting, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Dean Henson's Travel, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Dean Lamar, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Dining Hall Fines, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Dining Hall Policy, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Directory Information (Policy Statement on Release), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Disciplinary Actions, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Disciplinary Actions, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Disciplinary Procedures of the Yale College Executive Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Draft: Non-registration for the Draft and Financial Aid, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Dwight Hall, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Elections, Class
    - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - 1984 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - 1986 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - 1987 Apr (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Candidacy Statements, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - ESC Workshops (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Executive Committee on Admissions Policy, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Faculty, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Fees, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Finance and Administration, 1973, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Fire Extinguishers, Violation of Use on Campus, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Fire Marshal Memos, 1981, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Floor Plans, Hendrie Hall, 1969, 1973, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Floor Plans, Hillhouse Ave. and Temple St., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Foundation Grant Information, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Freshman Admissions, 1985 January (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Freshman Admits, 1984 January (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Freshman Affairs, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Freshman Conference, Dwight Hall, 1976-1981 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Freshman Mailing
    - 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Problems, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Summer, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Summer: Yale College Council, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Freshman Orientation
    - 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - 1985 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - 1988 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - 1989 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Freshman Reallocation, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Freshman Reallocation, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Freshman Reorientation Activities, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Freshman Roster: Listed by College, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Freshmen: General, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Gnomon Copy, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Guest Accommodations at Yale, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Hendrie Hall, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Housing, On Campus, 1986 Spring (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Joint Council of Social Chairmen (JCSC)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Accounting Transfers, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Student Activities Cards
      - 1975-1981 (Box 2, Folder 104)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 105)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 106)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Student Activities Committee Information, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Student Activities Committee Policy, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Student Activities Committee, General (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Sponsored Activities, 1978-1984 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Latina Perspective, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Law School Film Society: Financial Information, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Legal Issues, 1974-1983 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Legal Issues, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 115)